{
	"cards": [
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-35-tag-multiple-choice-card-1",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"awareness to place, pink and dry skin, and consistent eye contact.",
					"crying or combativeness, good muscle tone, and awareness to time.",
					"normal interactiveness, awareness to time, and pink skin color.",
					"age-appropriate behavior, good muscle tone, and good eye contact."
				],
				"question": "A normal level of consciousness in an infant or child is characterized by:",
				"source": "See Patient Assessment"
			},
			"back": "age-appropriate behavior, good muscle tone, and good eye contact."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-35-tag-multiple-choice-card-2",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"a rash.",
					"ear pain.",
					"chills.",
					"a headache."
				],
				"question": "The EMT should be most concerned when a child presents with fever and:",
				"source": "See Fever Emergencies and Management"
			},
			"back": "a rash."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-35-tag-multiple-choice-card-3",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"stridorous breathing.",
					"a cough that resembles the bark of a seal.",
					"wheezing.",
					"a weak cough."
				],
				"question": "Signs of an upper airway obstruction in an infant or child include all of the following, except:",
				"source": "See Respiratory Emergencies and Management"
			},
			"back": "wheezing."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-35-tag-multiple-choice-card-4",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"put padding behind his or her head.",
					"place him or her on a firm surface.",
					"rule out an injury to the spinal cord.",
					"thoroughly suction his or her airway."
				],
				"question": "Before positioning an infant or child’s airway, you should:",
				"source": "See Patient Assessment"
			},
			"back": "place him or her on a firm surface."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-35-tag-multiple-choice-card-5",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"swimming pools.",
					"alcohol.",
					"hyperthermia.",
					"child abuse."
				],
				"question": "Submersion injuries in the adolescent age group are most commonly associated with:",
				"source": "See Drowning Emergencies and Management"
			},
			"back": "alcohol."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-35-tag-multiple-choice-card-6",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"gather critical data by performing a rapid hands-on assessment of the child.",
					"allow you to rapidly and visually form a general impression of the child.",
					"determine if the child’s vital signs are within the age-appropriate limits.",
					"facilitate a rapid head-to-toe assessment of the child by visualization only."
				],
				"question": "The purpose of the pediatric assessment triangle (PAT) is to:",
				"source": "See Patient Assessment"
			},
			"back": "allow you to rapidly and visually form a general impression of the child."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-35-tag-multiple-choice-card-7",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"excessive tearing.",
					"moist oral mucosa.",
					"bulging fontanelles.",
					"absent urine output."
				],
				"question": "An infant with severe dehydration would be expected to present with:",
				"source": "See Poisoning Emergencies and Management"
			},
			"back": "absent urine output."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-35-tag-multiple-choice-card-8",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"toddler period.",
					"premature phase.",
					"neonatal period.",
					"start of infancy."
				],
				"question": "The first month of life after birth is referred to as the:",
				"source": "See Growth and Development"
			},
			"back": "neonatal period."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-35-tag-multiple-choice-card-9",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"there is usually obvious injury to the external chest wall.",
					"the sudden force against the ribs causes them to fracture.",
					"the flexible rib cage protects the vital thoracic organs.",
					"the flexible ribs can be compressed without breaking."
				],
				"question": "When a child experiences a blunt chest injury:",
				"source": "See Pediatric Trauma Emergencies and Management"
			},
			"back": "the flexible ribs can be compressed without breaking."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-35-tag-multiple-choice-card-10",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"face",
					"back",
					"shins",
					"buttocks"
				],
				"question": "Bruising to the _________ is least suggestive of child abuse.",
				"source": "See Child Abuse and Neglect"
			},
			"back": "shins"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-35-tag-multiple-choice-card-11",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"are typically consistent among all age and weight groups.",
					"are most severe if the child ingested a poisonous substance.",
					"vary widely, depending on the child’s age and weight.",
					"usually present within the first 10 minutes of ingestion."
				],
				"question": "The signs and symptoms of poisoning in children:",
				"source": "See Poisoning Emergencies and Management"
			},
			"back": "vary widely, depending on the child’s age and weight."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-35-tag-multiple-choice-card-12",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"his or her respirations are shallow.",
					"his or her tidal volume is adequate.",
					"he or she is breathing inadequately.",
					"an oral airway has been inserted."
				],
				"question": "Use of a nonrebreathing mask or nasal cannula in a child is appropriate only if:",
				"source": "See Respiratory Emergencies and Management"
			},
			"back": "his or her tidal volume is adequate."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-35-tag-multiple-choice-card-13",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"positioning, ice packs, and extremity elevation.",
					"avoiding the placement of a splint, if possible.",
					"separating the child from his or her parents.",
					"heat compresses and lowering the injured extremity."
				],
				"question": "Effective methods for providing pain relief to a child with an extremity injury include:",
				"source": "See Pediatric Trauma Emergencies and Management"
			},
			"back": "positioning, ice packs, and extremity elevation."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-35-tag-multiple-choice-card-14",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"18 months and 10 years.",
					"8 months and 8 years.",
					"6 months and 6 years.",
					"3 months and 4 years."
				],
				"question": "Febrile seizures are most common in children between:",
				"source": "See Neurologic Emergencies and Management"
			},
			"back": "6 months and 6 years."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-35-tag-multiple-choice-card-15",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"hypothermia and an irregular pulse.",
					"a generalized rash with intense itching.",
					"a low-grade fever and tachycardia.",
					"cherry-red spots or a purplish rash."
				],
				"question": "Children with N. meningitides would most likely present with:",
				"source": "See Neurologic Emergencies and Management"
			},
			"back": "cherry-red spots or a purplish rash."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-35-tag-multiple-choice-card-16",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"use a toe-to-head assessment approach.",
					"talk to the child, not just the caregiver.",
					"rely solely on the parent for information.",
					"refrain from taking a blood pressure."
				],
				"question": "When assessing an 8-year-old child, you should:",
				"source": "See Growth and Development"
			},
			"back": "talk to the child, not just the caregiver."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-35-tag-multiple-choice-card-17",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"EMTs must report all suspected cases of child abuse.",
					"EMTs should document their perceptions on the run form.",
					"A supervisor can forbid an EMT from reporting possible abuse.",
					"Child abuse must be reported only if it can be proven."
				],
				"question": "Which of the following is true regarding the legal implications of child abuse?",
				"source": "See Child Abuse and Neglect"
			},
			"back": "EMTs must report all suspected cases of child abuse."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-35-tag-multiple-choice-card-18",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"is experiencing mild to moderate pain.",
					"has a possible closed fracture of the radius.",
					"falls from a height greater than 4 to 5 feet.",
					"has a history compatible with a serious illness."
				],
				"question": "Immediate transport is indicated for a child when he or she:",
				"source": "See Patient Assessment"
			},
			"back": "has a history compatible with a serious illness."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-35-tag-multiple-choice-card-19",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"place oxygen tubing through a hole in a paper cup.",
					"have a parent restrain the child as you give oxygen.",
					"use a nasal cannula instead of a nonrebreathing mask.",
					"tightly secure the oxygen mask straps to the face."
				],
				"question": "When administering oxygen to a frightened child, it would be most appropriate to:",
				"source": "See Respiratory Emergencies and Management"
			},
			"back": "place oxygen tubing through a hole in a paper cup."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-35-tag-multiple-choice-card-20",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"At this age, the infant typically sleeps for up to 8 hours a day.",
					"The infant is unable to turn his or her head and focus.",
					"The infant should be aroused easily from a sleeping state.",
					"A 3-month-old infant can distinguish a parent from a stranger."
				],
				"question": "Which of the following statements regarding a 3-month-old infant is correct?",
				"source": "See Growth and Development"
			},
			"back": "A 3-month-old infant can distinguish a parent from a stranger."
		}
	],
	"category": {
		"value": "chapter-35",
		"label": "Chapter 35"
	},
	"tags": [
		{
			"value": "multiple-choice",
			"label": "Multiple Choice"
		}
	]
}